Company of Heroes is a action, drama, war film directed by Don Michael Paul.
American soldiers lost behind enemy lines during the WWII make a
horrific discovery: Hitler has a super bomb in development.
Against all odds, they set out to find the scientist in
charge of the program who is looking to defect.
Dean Ranson, played by Tom Sizemore.
Nate, played by Chad Michael Collins.
Brent Willoughby, played by Vinnie Jones.
Luca Gruenewald, played by Jürgen Prochnow.
Ivan Puzharski, played by Dimitri Diatchenko.
Kestrel, played by Melia Kreiling.
Company of Heroes is a 2013 American direct-to-video war
thriller film directed by Don Michael Paul.
The screenplay was co-written by Danny Bilson and Paul De Meo.
It was loosely based on the video game of the same name.
De Meo would later write Company of Heroes 2.
The tone is emotional.